[BEA] You know what, Abi?
He went to see Billy first…
[SNIFFLING]
…before even coming to his own family.
What are we to him?
Trash?
Just trash.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[GRUNTS]
Where do you think you're going?
Damn you!
[GRUNTING, GROANING]
[BEA] Get off me!
You witch!
[GRUNTING, GROANING]
- [KICK LANDS]
- [GROANS]
What do you want, huh?
Is this what you want?
- Damn you, you witch! [SLAP LANDS]
- [BEA GROANING]
What more do you want from me, huh?!
Leave us alone! Damn you!
They just let Bea go?!
[BILLY] I'm tired of getting my hopes
up for nothing, Auntie.
So I'll put a stop to them myself.
Hello, Jordan? Where are you?
[JORDAN] Summit Bay Suites.
We've been here before.
This is where Peter was staying.
This can't be a coincidence.
[BILLY] Why?
[JORDAN] This is where
I traced the location
of the person who leaked LoveList's files.
[BILLY] Okay. I'm going there.
[JORDAN] Okay.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Dude. Where is she?
- I lost her.
- Huh?!
She suddenly disappeared!
I'm sorry. I asked reception,
but they don't want to tell me anything.
How did you lose her, Jordan?
Sorry.
Wait. Dude.
Is that Peter?
Remember the leaked files?
It was uploaded from this hotel.
[BILLY] You were talking to Bea.
Bea Mercado, right?
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
I'll tell you everything.
[BEA] Sir, wait a minute!
Wait a minute!
Mariela Mercado, we have
a warrant for your arrest.
Go away!
We are charging you
with qualified trespass to dwelling,
frustrated murder, and reckless
imprudence resulting in arson.
- Go ahead, cuff her!
- Sir, wait a minute!
Wait! Arrest me instead!
Spare my mother!
Take me instead! Please!
- You're all animals!
- Ma, no!
Cuff her!
Billy, please! Not my mother!
Take me instead!
What? Are you scared?
Don't worry.
Your daughter will be with you in jail.
We'll be the ones messing
with your life this time.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
Dude.
Finally!
It's over!
Damn you!
[MARIELA] You are the ones
who should go to prison!
You should pay!
I'll get back at you,
especially you, Billy.
I'll get back at you, you bastard!
[OFFICER] That's enough. Take her in.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[CAR HORN HONKING]
[SIREN BLARING]
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- [ENRICO] You bought a lot, huh?
- Daddy! [GIGGLES]
- [OLIVE] My goodness.
- Pa?
- [OLIVE] She's such a daddy's girl!
- [ENRICO] Are you happy now?
- [YOUNG BILLY] Yes. Thank you, Daddy.
- Pa?
- [WOMAN] Oh! Watch where you're going.
- [ENRICO] Okay, let's go.
[OLIVE] Come on, let's hurry up.
Wear your seat belt, dear.
[YOUNG BILLY GIGGLING] Yes.
- [OLIVE] We're so happy.
- [BEA] Pa.
Pa. Pa!
Pa!
Pa.
But the question is,
which one of us is the bigger thief?
A thief?
What the hell are you talking about?
If only you knew.
Knew what?
Why don't you just tell the truth,
so I can understand
where your anger is coming from?
What's your reason for going after me?
Ma. Ma!
Let go of my mother.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Leave my daughter alone!
- Ma.
- Karma will get you one day!
I'll be waiting.
I can't bear to see you suffer, my dear.
Me? Suffering?
I'm not suffering.
I never said I was suffering.
I'll find a way.
I'll get a job and then…
I'll get back at Billy.
I promise you. I'll make her pay.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Caloy, I don't understand.
I've done everything I can
to give my mother a good life.
[BEA SNIFFLES]
What's happening?
I'm back to square one.
I want Billy's life
because it should've been mine.
That should've been mine,
but Billy just had to steal it!
[POLICE SIREN WAILING]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES, FADES]
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC CONTINUES, FADES]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKING]
[INMATE 1] Wow.
[INMATES CHATTERING]
- What good skin.
- She's pretty.
[CUFFS CLINKING]
[CELL LOCK RATTLING]
[CELL DOOR OPENS]
[CUFFS CLINKING]
- [CELL DOOR CLOSES]
- Ma, sit down.
[CELL LOCK RATTLING]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES, FADES]
[BILLY] Um, Auntie Pres,
this will be your room.
And this'll be mine.
And Oliver will stay there.
As well as Dad.
- Mmm.
- [PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
You're letting your father
live here with us?
Are you sure about this, Billy?
What he did to my brother and me
isn't easy to forget.
But I also can't forget
what he did for us.
Mmm.
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MUSIC BECOMES GENTLE]
[CAR DOOR OPENS]
[WHEELCHAIR RATTLING]
Go easy.
[BILLY] Here, Dad.
- [ENRICO] Okay.
- Okay.
- [BILLY] One, two, three.
- [OLIVER] Two, one.
[PRECIOUS] I'll take care of it.
[WHEELCHAIR RATTLING]
[BILLY] Everything okay, Dad?
Okay.
[CAR DOOR OPENS]
Oh.
[OLIVER] Auntie.
Thank you. Pa.
Careful. Oops.
[ENRICO GROANING]
[OLIVER] Pa.
- Here, Pa.
- [GROANS]
Oh.
Pa, did you know that we're
sharing a room?
- Really?
- Come on, let's go!
[OLIVER] Pa, hurry!
[GENTLE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[OLIVER] As long as you
let me secure my spot!
Pa, look at this.
I had this printed myself!
Looks good, huh?
Before, we used to just be
together in photos.
Now, we really are together!
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC PLAYING]
Pa?
[ENRICO CRYING]
Pa.
Pa?
[KEEPS CRYING]
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
Thank you.
[SOFT THUD]
[LIGHTLY KNOCKING]
Ah, come in, Billy.
Um…
You left some of your other stuff
at the apartment.
I'll go back and get it.
No, let me.
I found these.
I've read all of them too.
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC PLAYING]
Those were for every year
that I couldn't be with you, Billy.
Thank you for letting me stay here.
I just want to express my gratitude.
If it weren't for you, I probably…
I probably wouldn't be
with Auntie Pres and Oliver.
You shouldn't feel like
you owe me anything, Billy.
I'm the one who made
many mistakes.
so many wrong decisions.
Billy.
Would it be okay if I asked for a hug?
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MUSIC SWELLS]
[SOBBING]
[SNIFFLES]
[MUSIC FADES]
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Auntie Pres.
Your father
is asking about the fire.
He wants to know what really happened.
What did you say, Auntie?
I told him what you told me.
That it was an accident.
The doctors specifically told us
that he isn't allowed to be stressed.
It might stress him out
if he finds out someone is bothering us.
[PRECIOUS] Hmm.
It's good that it's not on the news much.
It's good that he doesn't know
what really happened.
And besides, they're both in jail now.
Thank God.
I can finally sleep peacefully.
Me too, Auntie.
I'll focus on LoveList first.
I have a lot I need to recover.
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING, FADES]
Ma.
No matter what happens,
don't tell them
that you know
they're Papa's second family.
Why not?
That's the truth.
Ma.
Please listen to me.
That's a strong motive.
It'll just prove that you're going after
Papa's illegitimate child.
We'll get into more trouble.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
But
shouldn't they be the ones to suffer?
Right?
Not us.
Especially not you.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I dragged you into this.
[SNIFFLES]
I never meant for this to happen.
But when I saw their house burning down,
I thought that they deserved it.
So they could go through
what happened to us.
What happened to your sister.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
But it's also my fault, Ma.
I was followed. [CLICKS TONGUE]
They tracked us down,
and now look where we are.
Behind bars.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
I will do everything possible, Ma.
I will do everything I can
to get you out of here.
Not just me.
Both of us.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SNIFFLES]
[MAN] I'm afraid I have some bad news.
Your eldest daughter, Abigail?
She died in a fire.
Abi, dear…
I promise
I will find your mother and sister.
Billy, are you sure you're ready?
We don't really have a choice.
LoveList can't afford to slow down now.
So to start,
Claire Fabrizio
has officially expressed her interest
in investing in LoveList's
global expansion.
Peter's wife?
We really don't have a choice.
We need to close this deal
with Claire Fabrizio.
Okay?
Multiple charges were filed against you.
You need to apologize to the victim.
I should apologize?!
I will never apologize to that woman!
I don't know if Billy will ever
be able to forgive me
for what I'm about to tell her.
I know this is too much.
But she needs to
know the truth.
You need to tell me why
you're so angry at Ms. Cariño.